const questions = [
    { 
        "category": "Accounting Principles(1)",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Which of the following is not a step in the accounting process ?",
        "correct_answer": "verification",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "identification",
          "recording",
          "communication"
        ]
      },
    {
        "category": "Accounting Principles(1)",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Financial accounting provides internal reports to help users make decisions about their companies ?",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "False",
          "Maybe Yes,Maybe No",
          "all of these"
        ]
      },
    {
        "category": "Accounting Principles(1)",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Which of the following statements about users of accounting information is incorrect?",
        "correct_answer": "Regulatory authorities are internal users.",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "Present creditors are external users.",
          "Taxing authorities are external users.",
          "Management is an internal user."
        ]
      },
    {
        "category": "Accounting Principles(1)",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Which of the following would not be considered an internal user of accounting data for a company",
        "correct_answer": " controller of the company",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "production manager",
          " Internal Revenue Service",
          "president of the company"
        ]
      },
    {
        "category": "Accounting Principles(1)",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Ethics are the standards of conduct by which one's actions are judged as",
        "correct_answer": "all of these",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "honest or dishonest",
          "right or wrong",
          "fair or unfair"
        ]
      },
    {
        "category": "Accounting Principles(1)",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The cost principle states that ?",
        "correct_answer": " assets should be recorded at their cost.",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "only transaction data capable of being expressed in terms of money be included in the accounting records",
          "activities of an entity are to be kept separate and distinct from its owner.",
          "assets should be initially recorded at cost and adjusted when the fair value changes."
        ]
      },
    {
        "category": "Accounting Principles(1)",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "The three types of business entities are ?",
        "correct_answer": " proprietorships, partnerships, and corporations",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "proprietorships, small businesses, and partnerships",
          "proprietorships, partnerships, and large businesses",
          "financial, manufacturing, and service companies"
        ]
      },
    {
        "category": "Accounting Principles(1)",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "At the beginning of the year, Kimball Company had total assets of $700,000 and total liabilities of $400,000. If the total assets increased $100,000 and the total liabilities decreased $80,000, what is the amount of owner's equity at the end of the year?",
        "correct_answer": "$480,000",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "$3000,000",
          "20,000",
          "cannot be determined from the data given"
        ]
      },
    {
        "category": "Accounting Principles(1)",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Performing services on account will have the following effects on the components of the basic accounting equation:",
        "correct_answer": "increase assets and increase owner's equity",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "increase assets and decrease owner's equity",
          "increase assets and increase liabilities",
          "increase liabilities and increase owner's equity"
        ]
      },
    {
        "category": "Accounting Principles(1)", // this is here (10) question in Accounting Principles(1)
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": " The statement of cash flows provides information on the cash receipts and payments for a specific period of time.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "False",
          "maybe yes,maybe No",
          "all of these"
        ]
      },
    {
        "category": "Managerial Accounting",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Molina Company has beginning and ending work in process inventories of $130,000 and $145,000 respectively. If total manufacturing costs are $650,000, what is the total cost of goods manufactured?",
        "correct_answer": "$635,000",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "$780,000",
          "$780,000",
          "$665,000"
        ]
      },
    {
        "category": "Managerial Accounting",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Barton Company has beginning work in process inventory of $144,000 and total manufacturing costs of $686,000. If cost of goods manufactured is $640,000, what is the cost of the ending work in process inventory?",
        "correct_answer": "$190,000",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "$210,000",
          "$198,000",
          "$170,000"
        ]
      },
    {
        "category": "Managerial Accounting",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Which of the following costs are classified as a period cost?",
        "correct_answer": "Wages paid to a cost accounting department supervisor.",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "Wages paid to a factory custodian",
          "Wages paid to a production department supervisor.",
          "Wages paid to an assembly worker"
        ]
      },
    {
        "category": "Managerial Accounting",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Which of the following is not an element of manufacturing overhead?",
        "correct_answer": "Sales manager’s salary.",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "Plant manager’s salary.",
          "Factory repairman’s wages.",
          "Product inspector’s salary"
        ]
      },
    {
        "category": "Managerial Accounting",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": " Indirect labor is a:",
        "correct_answer": "product cost.",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "period cost.",
          "raw material cost.",
          "nonmanufacturing cost."
        ]
      },
    {
        "category": "Managerial Accounting",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Gammil Company has beginning and ending raw materials inventories of $96,000 and $120,000, respectively. If direct materials used were $440,000, what was the cost of raw materials purchased?",
        "correct_answer": "$464,000",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "$416,000",
          "$470,000",
          "$440,000"
        ]
      },
    {
        "category": "Managerial Accounting",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Which of the following managerial accounting techniques attempts to allocate manufacturing overhead in a more meaningful fashion?",
        "correct_answer": "Activity-based costing",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "Balanced scorecard.",
          "Total quality management.",
          "Just-in-time inventory."
        ]
      },
    {
        "category": "Managerial Accounting",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "After passage of the Sarbanes-Oxley Act:",
        "correct_answer": "CEOs and CFOs must certify that financial statements give a fair presentation of the company’s operating results",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "reports prepared by managerial accountants must by audited by CPAs",
          "the audit committee, rather than top management, is responsible for the company’s financial statements.",
          "reports prepared by managerial accountants must comply with generally accepted accounting principles (GAAP)"
        ]
      },
    {
        "category": "Managerial Accounting",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": " Which of the following costs would a computer manufacturer include in manufacturing overhead?",
        "correct_answer": "Depreciation on testing equipment.",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "The cost of the memory chips.",
          "The wages earned by computer assemblers.",
          "The cost of the disk drives."
        ]
      },
    {
        "category": "Managerial Accounting",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "The formula to determine the cost of goods manufactured is:",
        "correct_answer": "Beginning work in process inventory + Total manufacturing costs - Ending work in process inventory",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "Beginning finished good inventory + Total manufacturing costs - Ending finished goods inventory.",
          "Beginning work in process inventory + Total manufacturing costs - Ending finished goods inventory",
          "Beginning raw materials inventory + Total manufacturing costs - Ending work in process inventory"
        ]
      },
    {
        "category": "Managerial Accounting",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Managerial accounting:",
        "correct_answer": "places emphasis on special-purpose information",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "is governed by generally accepted accounting",
          "pertains to the entity as a whole and is highly",
          "is limited to cost data"
        ]
      },
    {
        "category": "Managerial Accounting",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "A cost of goods manufactured schedule shows beginning and ending inventories for:",
        "correct_answer": "raw materials and work in process only .",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "work in process only",
          "raw materials only",
          "raw materials, work in process, and finished goods"
        ]
      },
    {
        "category": "Managerial Accounting", // this is here (13) question in Managerial Accounting
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Cost of goods available for sale is a step in the calculation of cost of goods sold of:",
        "correct_answer": "a merchandising company and a manufacturing company",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "neither a manufacturing company nor a merchandising company",
          "a manufacturing company but not a merchandising company",
          "a merchandising company but not a manufacturing company"
        ]
      },
   

]

// questions.forEach(question => {
//  Result = [];
 
//  if("name" == question.category && "difficulty" == question.difficulty ){

//  }else if(){

//  }

// });



